http://www.moresecure.co.uk/privacy

About Us
Which website do you want to go to?
Forms
Contact Us
Which Apex site do you want to go to?
GDPR - Your Rights
You may request a copy of the personal data we hold about you and you may object to our processing of it (including by way of direct marketing) or ask us to rectify it, restrict the way in which we process it or delete it from our records.
Where we use or store personal information relating to you, you have the following rights:
• The right to be informed
• The right of access
• The right to rectification
• The right to erasure
• The right to restrict processing
• The right to data portability
• The right to object
• Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling.
For further information, we have provided a link to the Information Commissioner’s Office’s for additional guidance - Please click here
(1) What information do we collect?
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:
(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website.
(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services.
(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us.
(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters.
(e) any other information that you choose to send to us.
(2) Cookies
2. VISITORS TO OUR WEBSITE
2.1 We may collect and process personal data about you in the following circumstances:
2.1.1 when you complete forms on our website (“Site”). This includes your email address, name, contact telephone number, address, which is provided at the time of registering to use our Site, subscribing to our services, requesting further services;
2.1.2 whenever you provide information to us when reporting a problem with our Site, making a complaint, making an enquiry or contacting us for any other reason. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence;
2.1.3 details of your visits to our Site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise, and the resources that you access (see section 2.2.2 on Cookies below); and
2.1.4 whenever you disclose your information to us, or we collect information from you in any other way, through our Site.
2.2 We may also collect data in the following ways:
IP Address
2.2.1 We may collect information about your device, including where available your Internet Protocol address, for reasons of fraud protection. We may also collect information about your device’s operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.
Cookies
2.2.2 Our Site uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our Site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Site and also allows us to improve our Site.
2.3 We may use your personal data for the legitimate interests of Storage Direct in order to:
2.3.1 provide you with information, or services that you requested from us;
2.3.2 allow you to participate in interactive features of our Site, when you choose to do so;
2.3.3 ensure that content from our Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your device;
2.3.4 improve our Site and services;
2.3.5 process and deal with any complaints or enquiries made by you; and
2.3.6 contact you for marketing purposes where you have signed up for these (see section 6 for further details).
Website Links
Our Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of third parties. Please note that if you follow a link to any of these websites, such websites will apply different terms to the collection and privacy of your personal data and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check before you submit your information to these websites.
How we use cookies
Our website uses 10 cookies. These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and to improve our website. We are required by law to provide you with clear and comprehensive information about the cookies that we use and if this page does not answer all of your queries you should contact us.
Our cookies do not store information which could be used to identify you personally, such as your contact details.
We use the following cookies:
Strictly Necessary Cookies
These are cookies that are required for the operation of our website. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website, use a shopping cart or make use of e-billing services.
Analytical/Performance Cookies
They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.
Functionality Cookies
These are used to recognise you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalise our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).
Targeting Cookies
These cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make our website and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose.
You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them in the table below:
Cookie Name
Purpose
vscommerce
A session identifier cookie that disappears after the browser is closed. This is a unique ID that references the database entry holding information such as the basket contents, logged in status and other information.
VSReferrer
An identifier that stores that website that referred you
VSCurrency
An identifier that references the currency the prices are displayed in.
VSVatPrices
An identifier that references if prices are shown inclusive or exclusive of VAT.
VSCategoryGroup
An identifier that references the last top level category visited.
VSCourierID
An identifier that references the courier the customer has selected.
VSCountryID
An identifier that references the country the customer has selected.
affiliate_source
Details of which Affiliate scheme referred the visitor to the website - such as Webgains or Affiliate Window.
vs_login
Secure login token if the visitor selected for the website to remember them.
Google Analytics
Non-personal information used to track a visitors route through the website. This is used to find at which point customers have abandoned the checkout process and is used to improve the website. You can read more information on the cookies used by Google Analytics uses on its information page
How do i block cookies?
Storage Direct website does work at its best when all cookies are enabled, and will provide the best browsing experience only if all cookies are enabled. You can turn-off advertising and social media cookies using the slider bar below:
What Will Happen If I Disable Cookies?
If you choose to disable access to cookies on your browser you will not be able to login, register or purchase from this website.
Information on how to disable cookies in popular web browsers can be found below:
PC Instructions
MAC Instructions
Firefox 13 and newer
At the top of the Firefox window, click on the Firefox button (Tools menu in Windows XP) and then click 'Options'
Then select the 'Privacy' icon
Set the 'Use custom settings for history' in the 'Firefox will' dropdown
Untick 'Accept cookies from sites' to disable cookies
Firefox 13 and newer
At the top of the Firefox window, click on the Firefox button and then click 'Options'
Then select the 'Privacy' icon
Set the 'Use custom settings for history' in the 'Firefox will' dropdown
Untick 'Accept cookies from sites'
Google Chrome
Click on the tool icon at the top right of your browser window and select 'Settings'
Click the 'Show advanced settings' link, locate the 'Privacy' section, and select the 'Content settings' button
Now select 'Block sites from setting any data'
Google Chrome
Click on 'Tools' at the top of your browser window and select 'Options'
Click the 'Under the Hood' tab, locate the 'Privacy' section, and select the 'Content settings' button
Now select 'Block sites from setting any data'
Internet Explorer
Click on 'Tools' at the top of your browser window and select 'Internet options', then click on the 'Privacy' tab
Under 'Settings' move the slider to the top to block all cookies
Internet Explorer
N/A
Microsoft Edge
Click on the three-dot 'More' icon in the top right then select 'Settings' from the menu
Scroll down to the bottom of the settings menu and click 'View Advanced Settings'
Under the 'Cookies' field press the dropdown arrow and select 'Block All Cookies'
Microsoft Edge
N/A
Safari
N/A
Safari
Click on 'Safari' at the top of your browser window and select the 'Preferences' option
Click on 'Security' then choose 'Accept cookies'
Select the 'Never' option
Opera
Click on the Opera icon in the top left of the window
Select 'Settings' and choose 'Quick Preferences'
Uncheck 'Enable Cookies'
Opera
Click on the Opera icon in the top left of the window
Select 'Settings' and choose 'Quick Preferences'
Uncheck 'Enable Cookies'
Google Advertising
We organise visitors to the website into audiences based on which pages you view on the website. This helps us to see which products or product areas you are interested in. We then use this anonymous data to make our marketing through the Google Content Network and its Partner sites more targeted toward your interests. This is done by storing a cookie as described above which can last for any period of up to 540days, but will be disabled once you have purchased from the site. You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies for advertising by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or by clearing your cookies after a visit to our site.
User Log-In Caching
Within this Web Site cookies may in the future be used to save the visitor’s password (if and when this facility is provided) so that it does not have to be re-entered at each new visit.
If the user has chosen “remember login and password”, the following two items above will be encoded within cookies:
A unique Customer ID.
A login state.
If a “registered” user to this Web Site returns to the site without logging in, the ID stored in the cookie can be used to track the user (unless the user manually deleted the cookie, at which point the server may automatically regenerate another cookie).
(3) Using your personal data
Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.
We may use your personal information to:
(a) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;
(b) send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;
(c) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;
(d) send you general commercial communications;
(e) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
(f) send to you [our newsletter and other] marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by post or by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications)
(g) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; and
We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.
All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, Worldpay. You should only provide your personal information to Worldpay after reviewing the Worldpay privacy policy. We will share information with Worldpay only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website.
(4) Disclosures
We may disclose information about you to [any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors] in so far as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.
In addition, we may disclose information about you:
(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and
(d) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.
(5) Policy amendments
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.
We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.
(6) Third party websites
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
(7) Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.
(8) Contact
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to info@whittan-storage.com
Privacy
How we store and handle your private information and data
GDPR - Your Rights
You may request a copy of the personal data we hold about you and you may object to our processing of it (including by way of direct marketing) or ask us to rectify it, restrict the way in which we process it or delete it from our records.
Where we use or store personal information relating to you, you have the following rights:
• The right to be informed
• The right of access
• The right to rectification
• The right to erasure
• The right to restrict processing
• The right to data portability
• The right to object
• Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling.
For further information, we have provided a link to the Information Commissioner’s Office’s for additional guidance - Please click here
(1) What information do we collect?
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:
(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website.
(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services.
(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us.
(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters.
(e) any other information that you choose to send to us.
(2) Cookies
2. VISITORS TO OUR WEBSITE
2.1 We may collect and process personal data about you in the following circumstances:
2.1.1 when you complete forms on our website (“Site”). This includes your email address, name, contact telephone number, address, which is provided at the time of registering to use our Site, subscribing to our services, requesting further services;
2.1.2 whenever you provide information to us when reporting a problem with our Site, making a complaint, making an enquiry or contacting us for any other reason. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence;
2.1.3 details of your visits to our Site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise, and the resources that you access (see section 2.2.2 on Cookies below); and
2.1.4 whenever you disclose your information to us, or we collect information from you in any other way, through our Site.
2.2 We may also collect data in the following ways:
IP Address
2.2.1 We may collect information about your device, including where available your Internet Protocol address, for reasons of fraud protection. We may also collect information about your device’s operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.
Cookies
2.2.2 Our Site uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our Site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Site and also allows us to improve our Site.
2.3 We may use your personal data for the legitimate interests of Storage Direct in order to:
2.3.1 provide you with information, or services that you requested from us;
2.3.2 allow you to participate in interactive features of our Site, when you choose to do so;
2.3.3 ensure that content from our Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your device;
2.3.4 improve our Site and services;
2.3.5 process and deal with any complaints or enquiries made by you; and
2.3.6 contact you for marketing purposes where you have signed up for these (see section 6 for further details).
Website Links
Our Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of third parties. Please note that if you follow a link to any of these websites, such websites will apply different terms to the collection and privacy of your personal data and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check before you submit your information to these websites.
How we use cookies
Our website uses 10 cookies. These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and to improve our website. We are required by law to provide you with clear and comprehensive information about the cookies that we use and if this page does not answer all of your queries you should contact us.
Our cookies do not store information which could be used to identify you personally, such as your contact details.
We use the following cookies:
Strictly Necessary Cookies
These are cookies that are required for the operation of our website. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website, use a shopping cart or make use of e-billing services.
Analytical/Performance Cookies
They allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.
Functionality Cookies
These are used to recognise you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalise our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).
Targeting Cookies
These cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make our website and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose.
You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them in the table below:
Cookie Name
Purpose
vscommerce
A session identifier cookie that disappears after the browser is closed. This is a unique ID that references the database entry holding information such as the basket contents, logged in status and other information.
VSReferrer
An identifier that stores that website that referred you
VSCurrency
An identifier that references the currency the prices are displayed in.
VSVatPrices
An identifier that references if prices are shown inclusive or exclusive of VAT.
VSCategoryGroup
An identifier that references the last top level category visited.
VSCourierID
An identifier that references the courier the customer has selected.
VSCountryID
An identifier that references the country the customer has selected.
affiliate_source
Details of which Affiliate scheme referred the visitor to the website - such as Webgains or Affiliate Window.
vs_login
Secure login token if the visitor selected for the website to remember them.
Google Analytics
Non-personal information used to track a visitors route through the website. This is used to find at which point customers have abandoned the checkout process and is used to improve the website. You can read more information on the cookies used by Google Analytics uses on its information page
How do i block cookies?
Storage Direct website does work at its best when all cookies are enabled, and will provide the best browsing experience only if all cookies are enabled. You can turn-off advertising and social media cookies using the slider bar below:
What Will Happen If I Disable Cookies?
If you choose to disable access to cookies on your browser you will not be able to login, register or purchase from this website.
Information on how to disable cookies in popular web browsers can be found below:
PC Instructions
MAC Instructions
Firefox 13 and newer
At the top of the Firefox window, click on the Firefox button (Tools menu in Windows XP) and then click 'Options'
Then select the 'Privacy' icon
Set the 'Use custom settings for history' in the 'Firefox will' dropdown
Untick 'Accept cookies from sites' to disable cookies
Firefox 13 and newer
At the top of the Firefox window, click on the Firefox button and then click 'Options'
Then select the 'Privacy' icon
Set the 'Use custom settings for history' in the 'Firefox will' dropdown
Untick 'Accept cookies from sites'
Google Chrome
Click on the tool icon at the top right of your browser window and select 'Settings'
Click the 'Show advanced settings' link, locate the 'Privacy' section, and select the 'Content settings' button
Now select 'Block sites from setting any data'
Google Chrome
Click on 'Tools' at the top of your browser window and select 'Options'
Click the 'Under the Hood' tab, locate the 'Privacy' section, and select the 'Content settings' button
Now select 'Block sites from setting any data'
Internet Explorer
Click on 'Tools' at the top of your browser window and select 'Internet options', then click on the 'Privacy' tab
Under 'Settings' move the slider to the top to block all cookies
Internet Explorer
N/A
Microsoft Edge
Click on the three-dot 'More' icon in the top right then select 'Settings' from the menu
Scroll down to the bottom of the settings menu and click 'View Advanced Settings'
Under the 'Cookies' field press the dropdown arrow and select 'Block All Cookies'
Microsoft Edge
N/A
Safari
N/A
Safari
Click on 'Safari' at the top of your browser window and select the 'Preferences' option
Click on 'Security' then choose 'Accept cookies'
Select the 'Never' option
Opera
Click on the Opera icon in the top left of the window
Select 'Settings' and choose 'Quick Preferences'
Uncheck 'Enable Cookies'
Opera
Click on the Opera icon in the top left of the window
Select 'Settings' and choose 'Quick Preferences'
Uncheck 'Enable Cookies'
Google Advertising
We organise visitors to the website into audiences based on which pages you view on the website. This helps us to see which products or product areas you are interested in. We then use this anonymous data to make our marketing through the Google Content Network and its Partner sites more targeted toward your interests. This is done by storing a cookie as described above which can last for any period of up to 540days, but will be disabled once you have purchased from the site. You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies for advertising by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or by clearing your cookies after a visit to our site.
User Log-In Caching
Within this Web Site cookies may in the future be used to save the visitor’s password (if and when this facility is provided) so that it does not have to be re-entered at each new visit.
If the user has chosen “remember login and password”, the following two items above will be encoded within cookies:
A unique Customer ID.
A login state.
If a “registered” user to this Web Site returns to the site without logging in, the ID stored in the cookie can be used to track the user (unless the user manually deleted the cookie, at which point the server may automatically regenerate another cookie).
(3) Using your personal data
Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.
We may use your personal information to:
(a) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;
(b) send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;
(c) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;
(d) send you general commercial communications;
(e) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
(f) send to you [our newsletter and other] marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by post or by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications)
(g) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; and
We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.
All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, Worldpay. You should only provide your personal information to Worldpay after reviewing the Worldpay privacy policy. We will share information with Worldpay only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website.
(4) Disclosures
We may disclose information about you to [any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors] in so far as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.
In addition, we may disclose information about you:
(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and
(d) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.
(5) Policy amendments
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.
We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.
(6) Third party websites
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
(7) Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.
(8) Contact
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to info@whittan-storage.com
Which website do you want to go to?
Forms
Contact Us
Which Apex site do you want to go to?
Please tick this box if you are happy to be contacted by email or phone.
Submit
